let deckList = [
    {
        deckID: 1,
        deckDesc: 'Logic Design'
    },
    {
        deckID: 2,
        deckDesc: 'Calculus'
    },
];

let cardList = [
    {
        cardID: 1,
        deckID: 1,
        cardQuestion: 'a + b = ?',
        cardHint: 'Commutative Property',
        cardAnswer: 'a + b = b + a',
        cardImageQuestion: '',
        cardImageHint: '',
        cardImageAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        cardID: 2,
        deckID: 1,
        cardQuestion: 'ab = ?',
        cardHint: 'Commutative Property',
        cardAnswer: 'ab = ba',
        cardImageQuestion: '',
        cardImageHint: '',
        cardImageAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        cardID: 3,
        deckID: 1,
        cardQuestion: 'a + (b + c) = ?',
        cardHint: 'Associative Property',
        cardAnswer: 'a + (b + c) = (a + b) + c',
        cardImageQuestion: '',
        cardImageHint: '',
        cardImageAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        cardID: 4,
        deckID: 1,
        cardQuestion: 'a(bc) = ?',
        cardHint: 'Associative Property',
        cardAnswer: 'a(bc) = (ab)c',
        cardImageQuestion: '',
        cardImageHint: '',
        cardImageAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        cardID: 5,
        deckID: 1,
        cardQuestion: 'a + 0 = ?',
        cardHint: 'Identity Property',
        cardAnswer: 'a + 0 = a',
        cardImageQuestion: '',
        cardImageHint: '',
        cardImageAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        cardID: 6,
        deckID: 1,
        cardQuestion: 'a * 1 = ?',
        cardHint: 'Identity Property',
        cardAnswer: 'a * 1 = a',
        cardImageQuestion: '',
        cardImageHint: '',
        cardImageAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        cardID: 7,
        deckID: 1,
        cardQuestion: 'a + 1 = ?',
        cardHint: 'Null Property',
        cardAnswer: 'a + 1 = 1',
        cardImageQuestion: '',
        cardImageHint: '',
        cardImageAnswer: ''
    },
    {
        cardID: 8,
        deckID: 1,
        cardQuestion: 'a * 0 = ?',
        cardHint: 'Null Property',
        cardAnswer: 'a * 0 = 0',
        cardImageQuestion: '',
        cardImageHint: '',
        cardImageAnswer: ''
    },
];